<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Tribe</string>
    <string name="review_listing">Review Listing</string>
    <string name="review_details">Review Details</string>
    <string name="remote_service_url">http://grapevine-ws.heroku.com/reviews</string>
    <string name="request_token">e3e5f11e6c9cd54fc0fce481cf10f091</string>
    <string name="no_reviews">No Reviews to display.</string>
    <string name="loading_reviews">Loading Reviews...</string>
    <string name="pref_activity">Preferences</string>
    <string name="camera_activity">Camera</string>
    <string name="map_activity">MapView</string>
    <string name="show_on_map">Show on Map</string>
    <string name="new_review_activity">NewReview</string>
    <string name="settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="about">About</string>
    <string name="quit">Quit</string>
    <string name="upload_error_bar_message">Tribe Alert</string>
    <string name="upload_error_heading">Twitter Credentials Invalid</string>
    <string name="upload_error_msg">Reviews not created. Invalid Credentials</string>
    <string name="following_tribe">You belong to tribe: </string>
    
    <string name="refresh_notification">Accuracy of tag locations depends on GPS/Network availability. It may take up to few minutes to sync.</string>
    <string name="setup_twitter_credentials">Please setup your Twitter user-name and password in preferences to post new reviews.</string>
    <string name="create_sqls">
    	CREATE TABLE REVIEWS ( id integer primary key, heading String, description String, is_like integer, image_url String, latitude String, longitude String, review_date String, username String, location_name String);
    	CREATE TABLE PENDING_REVIEWS ( id integer primary key, heading String, description String, is_like integer, image_url String, image_path String, latitude String, longitude String, review_date, username String, location_name String, creation_date Date, errors String, status String, retries integer);
    </string>
    <string name="thumbnail_url">http://twitpic.com/show/large/</string>
    <string name="mini_url">http://twitpic.com/show/mini/</string>
    <string name="app_description">
		Tribe is a platform for content aggregation, where content can be tagged using hashes. It leverages Twitter as a platform to share posted information and pictures; which gives the content visibility even outside Android on an existing social network. Some of the things that this app can allow you do are:
		\n\n1. Tag and lookup all the Blood Donors. Add contact or relevant information in text. Tribe #bloodDonors
		\n\n2. Tag and lookup all the Tourists attractions for the city. Tribe #tourists
		\n\n3. Tag and lookup all the cut down trees. Tribe #deforestation #lostTrees
		\n\n4. Tag and lookup all the ThoughtWorks conferences or events held. Tribe #thoughtworks #awayday
		\n\n5. Tag and lookup all the Social Impact programs around the city. Tribe #socialImpact
		\n\n6. Tag and lookup all bad experiences with local businesses. Beacon for others. Tribe #failBusiness #businessName
		\n\nDo not limit your imagination with the examples provided here. Generate unique content that people would love to follow. It\'s as simple as \"Point-Shoot Tag-Tweet\". Devise your own use of this app. Help \"them\", help yourself.
    </string>
</resources>
